<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-10-29T00:18:08-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">OgFOMK ArTS</title><subtitle>OgFOMK ArTS Blog </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Sin and Ignorance Leading Toward Forgetfulness</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/bible/2025/10/28/sin-and-ignorance-leading-toward-forgetfulness.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sin and Ignorance Leading Toward Forgetfulness" /><published>2025-10-28T18:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2025-10-28T18:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/bible/2025/10/28/sin-and-ignorance-leading-toward-forgetfulness</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/bible/2025/10/28/sin-and-ignorance-leading-toward-forgetfulness.html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
  <p>Numbers 15:25</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>And the priest shall make an atonement for all the congregation of the
children of Israel, and it shall be forgiven them; for it is ignorance: and
they shall bring their offering, a sacrifice made by fire unto the LORD, and their sin offering before the LORD, for their ignorance:</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Our sin is based on the idea that we wanted the tree of knowledge for wisdom. Our desire to be as gods when we were made in the image of God is corruption. We are ignorant because we are knowing and then not knowing by pride.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Genesis 2:17</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>But of the tree of the knowledge of good and evil, thou shalt not eat of
it: for in the day that thou eatest thereof thou shalt surely die.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Let’s look at sin. The sin is all action that is against the work of God. Working against God we hinder his production and work. Who are we to do this?</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Genesis 3:3-7</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>3 But of the fruit of the tree which is in the midst of the garden, God hath said, Ye shall not eat of it, neither shall ye touch it, lest ye die.</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>4 And the serpent said unto the woman, Ye shall not surely die:</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>5 For God doth know that in the day ye eat thereof, then your eyes shall be opened, and ye shall be as gods, knowing good and evil.</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>6 And when the woman saw that the tree was good for food, and that it was
pleasant to the eyes, and a tree to be desired to make one wise, she took of the fruit thereof, and did eat, and gave also unto her husband with her; and he did eat.</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>7 And the eyes of them both were opened, and they knew that they were naked; and they sewed fig leaves together, and made themselves aprons.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>We are the seed of the first man, Adam, and we are the seed of Noah, after the great flood. Today we are degenerate and corrupt beings leaving paradise, we were living 900 years and dying 6000 years ago. Today our modern dream worlds of gaming, fantasy, pornography, pharmaceutical superstition and sorcery are the bleeding edge of atrophy. We have called our secular trek evolution but we barely live beyond 90 years.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Genesis 5:5</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>And all the days that Adam lived were nine hundred and thirty years: and he died.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Hear the cries of the sophisticated man? He wants to never die, or he gives up it all for an Irish wake. He wants health care and population control. Secular nonsense is his wisdom.</p>

<p>In the study of the King James Bible we enter into an adventure that remits us to salvation. We find actual awakening into the work of the LORD. We get revival. We get our mind and brain physically transformed from trans-humanist lies to born again through Jesus Christ.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Bible" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Numbers 15:25]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How Much Money Is There?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/money/bible/blog/2025/10/27/how-much-money-is-there.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How Much Money Is There?" /><published>2025-10-27T18:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2025-10-27T18:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/money/bible/blog/2025/10/27/how-much-money-is-there</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/money/bible/blog/2025/10/27/how-much-money-is-there.html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>

</blockquote>

<p>How much money is there in this world? The answer is provided by those with divers measures. The fiat currency has no denominator. The LORD who is the master of measure must readjust the price because the resources are what the money buys and they, the resources, do not lie, unless they are measured diversely also.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Deuteronomy 25:13-15</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>13 Thou shalt not have in thy bag divers weights, a great and a small.</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>14 Thou shalt not have in thine house divers measures, a great and a small.</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>15 But thou shalt have a perfect and just weight, a perfect and just measure shalt thou have: that thy days may be lengthened in the land which the LORD thy God giveth thee.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Inflation is the unlimited money numerator printed in order to circumnavigate price discovery. One more thing that the praying man may understand is that this skill in precise measure affords him the blessing of the LORD in money. Not necessarily in wealth but in the understand of what divers measures are and also in not laying up treasure that is immeasurable.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Matthew 6:19-21</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>19 Lay not up for yourselves treasures upon earth, where moth and rust doth
corrupt, and where thieves break through and steal:</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>20 But lay up for yourselves treasures in heaven, where neither moth nor rust
doth corrupt, and where thieves do not break through nor steal:</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>21 For where your treasure is, there will your heart be also.</p>
</blockquote>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="money" /><category term="bible" /><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Work Without The Blessing</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2025/10/25/work-without-the-blessing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Work Without The Blessing" /><published>2025-10-25T18:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2025-10-25T18:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2025/10/25/work-without-the-blessing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2025/10/25/work-without-the-blessing.html"><![CDATA[<p>How do we do great work without the blessing of Jesus Christ? It is not possible. We hereby dedicate all of our work. writing, art, publishing, music and contract whims to the Lord Jesus Christ. All of our good work and all of our nonsense we give to Jesus as he can heal by being the Great Physician.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Matt 9:10-13</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>10 ¶ And it came to pass, as Jesus sat at meat in the house, behold, many publicans and sinners came and sat down with him and his disciples.</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>11 And when the Pharisees saw it, they said unto his disciples, Why eateth your Master with publicans and sinners?</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>12 But when Jesus heard that, he said unto them, They that be whole need not a physician, but they that are sick.</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>13 But go ye and learn what that meaneth, I will have mercy, and not sacrifice: for I am not come to call the righteous, but sinners to repentance.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Can I take OGFOMK and repurposed it as a blessing? Can I make this a vehicle for His namesake? Can I make a business or a ministry from speaking and writing about the wrong direction we are going? Can I also write about the good direction people are moving in?</p>

<p>One Giant Fart on Mankind should be repurposed. The attempt at renaming has been done before. Let’s do it again. Let us pray. Let us bow our heads and pray, We pray that the LORD will allow a new name to come from the old draught as fertilizer into the garden.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Matthew 15:17-19</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>17 Do not ye yet understand, that whatsoever entereth in at the mouth goeth
into the belly, and is cast out into the draught?</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>18 But those things which proceed out of the mouth come forth from the heart;
and they defile the man.</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>19 For out of the heart proceed evil thoughts, murders, adulteries,
fornications, thefts, false witness, blasphemies:</p>
</blockquote>

<h2 id="one-god-for-our-man-kind">One God For Our Man Kind</h2>

<p><img src="/assets/ogfomk-halo-big1-512.png" alt="OgFOMK ArTS Logo" /></p>

<h2 id="our-god-for-our-man-kind">Our God For Our Man Kind</h2>

<p>In our traditional OgFOMK logo the “g” was made small in order to separate the acronym from others. Also the little “g” looked nice when it was in a certain font. By no means are we saying that “g” is deprecating GOD and we are also not saying that we represent GOD. We are the servants of the LORD who is the Triune GOD - THE FATHER - THE SON and THE HOLY SPIRIT. We are the servants of the LORD Jesus Christ and we bow to him only!</p>

<p>Our logo is a legacy and we are moving into removing the fetters of our acts of abomination toward greater acts of testimony and service. Let us tell the truth about where we have been and where we are going.</p>

<p>Below is the Original Cover of Issue #1. What a mess! To say that this is embarrassing is an understatement but to also say that the demonic elements were also not there and that it was just mere blasphemy is also not true. This was a cover that our testimony can joyfully reject. We also don’t need to hide. Through Jesus Christ we are healed and we are forgiven. Not because of what we did, but because of what he, Jesus Christ, did for us!</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Philippians 4:6-7</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>6 Be careful for nothing; but in every thing by prayer and supplication with
thanksgiving let your requests be made known unto God.</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p>7 And the peace of God, which passeth all understanding, shall keep your
hearts and minds through Christ Jesus.</p>
</blockquote>

<p><img src="/assets/Zine-to-pdf-ogfomk01.png" alt="OgFOMK ArTS Issue #1, 1988" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do we do great work without the blessing of Jesus Christ? It is not possible. We hereby dedicate all of our work. writing, art, publishing, music and contract whims to the Lord Jesus Christ. All of our good work and all of our nonsense we give to Jesus as he can heal by being the Great Physician.]]></summary></entry></feed>